Hello friends, welcome to your
own channel D Retail Miss Me. Here I am going to
discuss friends a news due to
which this stock has fallen by more than two percent today.
And look, even if
you know the news, this video is
useful for you because this is not the first time that
a
notice has come from the department. Things have happened before
which show the stock to be very vulnerable or
a big threat for investors.
Friends, what is the whole matter? If you
are interested in stocks or are thinking of investing,
I think this video will be very useful for you.
But before moving forward,
friends, if you have come to this channel for the first time, then as I
make such videos,
for this, please subscribe to the channel and
like the video. Friends, now I am
taking you straight to it. Look at
ICC Lombard General Insurance Company
Limited. Okay, you see here
this stock is showing you a decline of more than two percent.
How much
decline of more than two percent is this stock showing you
and you will see that
if you look at this stock in the last one month, then it has shown a decline of more than 3% i.e. 4%.  Do
it, they have
shown the decline and if you look at it like this above, then the
stock has fallen by almost 7.30 percent,
friends, how much is 7.5 percent and
see, the
notation that the GST department has
received, this is not the first time, friends, the
stock has already received this
and right now the
fear is more because you must be aware that the GST
department is continuously
sending tax notices to all the companies, brother,
tax notices are being sent
to a company like Dream11,
it has given the biggest tax notice in the history of
about 40 thousand crore rupees,
friends, okay and this was very shocking, that is
why the notice that has come now is giving a big
blow to the investors, but after all,
what is the full news, after all, the full notice, so
see, for this I have gone to some news,
ICC Lombard Gate
1730 crore tax notice, yes, it is a
tax notice of 1730 crore and this is the
second time in 3 months, yes, as I have been saying
repeatedly, this is not the first time,
this is the second time it has been taken into notice in 3 months
Okay, how is this GI empty
but the note paying 1730 crore tax from
July 2017 to March 2022 okay,
I am not able to understand this, what is this brother
doing for the last three years okay, but okay, okay,
we have received a context demand,
so see, some small amount of 1730 crore was
taken out and given, if they have to pay it,
their situation will become tight okay,
you see here, brother Lombard,
where is it in an exchange final that they
received a show cost [ __ ] demand notice
from the Director General of GST
Intelligence under area 73 of the
Central Goods and Services Tax Act dated
September
27th, a demand of Rs
17,2200 crore, you can say that
they have received a demand of more than Rs 17,000 crore,
friends okay, now what is the benefit from the company's side, the
company says that the alert
demand has been made, the important show
cost [ __ ] demand notice on tension to non-
payment of GST on the insurance
premium  Expectedly, this is a follower
of coin transactions, non-PEI GST,
one combination accepted on the
insurance premium given to previous
Indian and foreign companies during the period
from 2017 to 22. Look, it is a small thing, there is
no need to complete it so much, you have to pay tax from 2017 to 22,
brother, that too
Rs 17,100 crore, I mean, this is a huge
amount, okay, and you
see, you will have to challenge such reports here,
if you have to pay so much
tax, the situation will worsen, and
you understand how big the tax is, that
in the quarter and one of June 2020, ICC
Lombard General Insurance
gave a net profit of ₹390 crore, that is, a
net profit of ₹390 crore, even if you
look at it, it will be a net profit of almost ₹400 crore for the entire year,
you have to pay this tax, which
means your situation is over, and that is why it is being said that the
applicants who have dared, have dared for this reason,
friends.  Okay, but we have to see
how things play out in the future. I'm
sweating over the constant
notifications from the GST department. This is a
not-so-good sign for the company.
This is a not-so-good sign for business and
environment. I don't understand
why this is happening, but
we'll have to see what happens next. But for now, it's
not good news. Friends, look, there's no problem in the company.
If you
look at the fundamentals, there won't be any issues
in the company. And this tax issue isn't
just for this company. So, I can't say that it's a
mistake from the company's side.
Look, the kind of environment we have right now. That's why the
stock market is a bit of a dangerous place.
If you're ever investing in the stock market, then the
risk that is repeatedly mentioned is
for this time period,
which you're seeing in stocks right now.
Okay, so now we'll have to see
how this pans out in the future. But this is a really
serious matter. The government should
definitely take cognizance of it. According to me, so stay tuned
here.
Thank you very much for this Yash know the video Jai
Hind